You know, this is a stock which is not for intraday but is
well positioned for the medium to long term.
It is a market leader in general insurance
and I feel that
if they have bought the stock, then they should keep a long-term time
frame. Although the price has fallen a bit in the short term,
but if their
view is at least for 12 to 15 months, then
I believe that post-
Covid general insurance will definitely see an
uptick and I feel that normality is gradually
returning.
Although the third variant of Om Nikon may have a
slight impact on the business,
but if their view is medium
to long term, then it is a very well-managed
blue chip company. This is a portfolio stock, so
I believe that money will definitely be made,
but it is important to keep the time frame and the time window at
least long. So, do
not be hasty here. Do not sell at a loss and if
possible, you can also average a little, but
keep a view of 12 to 15 months. Avinash, please give your opinion on this. South Indian
Bank is a slightly old purchase.  It was around ₹10
and now it is trading below ₹10.
Now, by averaging,
they have increased their quantity a little bit,
but we have seen that other
banks have done a little bit, big banks have given
good returns, some mid-cap
banks have done well, but
we have seen a range-bound trade in South Indian Bank
and we have always seen
that this stock stops around ₹10-12. What is
your current view on South Indian Bank? Are there
any signs of some reversal? Will its price
change or should the investment be switched from here?
Look Abhishek, I feel that
investors have put a lot of money in it
and I was hearing that they invested at ₹15-16.
Right now the stock is
below ₹10, so in my opinion, it should be held.
Look, the asset
quality and balance sheet of this bank are definitely fine,
but somewhere at the upper level,
selling pressure comes and we feel  There are
reports in the market that this bank will be taken over by a larger bank in the
future. If such an
event occurs, then definitely there could be a quick
rerating. Otherwise, they will have to
hold these shares for the long term. The
bank is profit-making, not loss-making,
and we feel that
some value buying may slowly emerge from this level,
provided they have some time. Although,
you know, this stock has
moved contrary to the outperformance of the markets. There has
n't been much outperformance, but
still, I believe that risk is completely factored in in the eight and nine rates. If there are no further
twists here, then the advice would be to hold here.
I feel that
hopefully, there could be a turnaround here within a year,
and they could get an exit here at least at their cost
price or slightly above that.
Avinash ji, please give your opinion on Avenue Supermarts.
See, the stock has generated tremendous profits,
and we saw prices up to 5900,
although after that a phase of consolidation followed.  This is
because there will be some
concerns about valuations now.
How are you viewing this company and their investment and
what advice would you have? When will this stock
start moving again?
Abhishek, I feel that
Avenue Supermarts is a company that has
shown significant outperformance since the time of its public issue. The
biggest thing here is basically the total addressable
market, which is the retail market in India, has
grown significantly. The
biggest speciality of Avenue Supermarts is that it is the
lowest cost retail player.
Most of its model is franchise led.
I feel that the way it is
adding new stores now, I feel that
growth will be good in the coming two-three years.
However, the price that the investor has
entered is definitely on the higher side. So,
if they want to
make good money from this investment, then keep a view of at least one and a half to two years
because valuations, as you
rightly said, are running at a significant premium
and until the earnings growth kicks off, the impact of the
coronavirus will remain.  There
is a scare, if the cases which are big in Mumbai right now do
not reduce then it is possible that we may
see some short term underperformance. But if the outlook is for one and a
half to two years, then I am confident that
D-Mar will bounce back well and
they will definitely get a better price than their cost price.
But it is important to keep the time frame long. So in
my opinion it is a good
stock but they have bought it at a slightly expensive
level, so keep the time frame long
and the opinion will be to hold it for at least one and a half to two years.
Avinash ji, what would be your opinion on realty?
We had seen that
a little bit of shine has returned to the real estate sector there
too, a little bit of re-rating has been
seen and if we look at the period from May to October,
we have seen a good growth in the stocks of all the companies there.
However, here also there is a
little pressure from the top, there is buying at 974,
but now it is trading around 850.
Realty companies are strong, are they
maintaining here too? Not yet, in fact
Abhishek, here also I think that see
if  If we look at Reality's business model, it
operates mostly in the Mumbai market. The
most important thing is that Reality is debt-free. It
manages projects very well. The
execution tracker is very good. Here
too, I believe that if their outlook is at
least a year or a year and a half, then the real
estate cycle has just begun. I
believe that in the coming year, that is 2022, there will be
good demand for residential space in the real estate market.
However, there is some concern in Reality markets
that if the interest rate cycle
increases, then there may be some loss
because obviously the cost of
funding loans will increase. But given their
track record and their projects,
there is a huge order book visibility.
I feel that if you have a
outlook of at least a year and a half, then hold it. The
stock may recover. There has been
some profit booking from the upper levels, but
I definitely expect the fundamentals to be good. If the outlook is good for next year, then the
fundamentals of Reality are
quite strong right now, both the company and the sector.
This counter can show good returns in the coming one to one and a half years. Let's take
another question.
Arvind Gautam ji has asked us a question. He
wants to know your opinion on Sequent Scientific.
And Avinash ji will take your opinion on this
because he wants to know about the fundamentals of the company.
Their buying price had
shown levels above ₹2000000 above the current price, but now if we
look at it, it has stood at around 150 level, that is,
around the price shown in December 2020. How do you
feel about the fundamentals of the company and some
targets are coming out on this, so
tell us about that also. Look, I feel that the
decline in Sequent Scientific is
mostly due to the economic crisis that has happened in Turkey. In fact, Sequent
Scientific has a huge exposure
here, but on the positive side,
if we look at this company, it works in a very unique
business, that is animal
health care, and which is very less in India.
Companies do this
and the biggest USP of this company
is that it operates globally and in many other
markets as well. In fact, recently the
P Fund has
bought a controlling stake here. I
feel that the year FY22 will be a
little volatile because not
only the currency but you know the
increase in Covid cases in the overall markets, due to this,
definitely this business may
see some ups and downs. But if we
talk about the longer term, if we talk about FY23 and FY24, then
hopefully, if everything goes
well, then there is definitely
no doubt that this company will do well in the future as well. In fact,
their investor
sentiment is definitely at a slightly higher level. If
they have a little risk appetite, then
I think they should average it back a little to 150
and at least I
think 250-275
is possible in the coming year and a half. And one more good
thing here.  It is true that a very large investor like HKN I has
already invested here,
plus P Fund of Carlyle is also quite big. Seeing
all these are indicators that the business has
long term viability. There will
definitely be some pain in the short term, but obviously once
Covid settles down and once
stability comes in the European market, then it will
return to normal in a good way. So I would
suggest averaging this level also,
but at least with a view of one and a half years,
okay,
see, in the long term, it
is definitely positive that the promoters have
bought Uno shares at around 00, but I think that
definitely, I mean, there is an
obviously an observation in the markets that compared to maybe
TCS, then Fossil, then Wipo,
if we look at HCL Tech, then
its valuation is already at a small
discount and it will be the same in the future as well
because obviously their margin
picture, their product book is
not that good compared to other companies, but still I  I would say those who have them should
hold on. I think
if the stock shows some softness in the short term,
you should
try to keep it a little
accumulative. If the price is positive, then it will definitely
make money in the medium to long term. But
yes, there will definitely be some volatility in the stock in the short term. So, you know, this is
definitely a buy-on-
decline stock. I feel that
if anyone still finds the valuation
cheap, it is because
if we look at the management quality here and other IT companies, then definitely they
get a discount here. So, continue to
hold on. If there is a big decline, then only there will be an
opportunity to buy.
I feel that Zomato
is such a company where you have to take a
view of at least two-three years. Right now the
company is loss-making, but
it is a very significant player in its field. I
feel that in the coming two-three years, the
company will hopefully be profitable. And the
kind of scale and technology backup
it has, investors should take a short call.  One should
invest in this, not from a term view but from a long view.
I feel that these are new generation
start-up companies, so the valuation
matrix that is being used here right now is price
to sales because there is no visibility of earnings at least
age of here. But
in the next two-three years, we feel that given the
kind of initiatives the company has not been taking, the
company will definitely become EBITDA positive
and this will create a lot of confidence in the markets. There is no
doubt that in the coming two-
three years, if you hold these 90 shares, there will be a
possibility of making good profits.
So keep a long-term time frame.
In the short term, there may be some negativity in the stock. The
company is making losses quarter by quarter.
But this is more or less on expected lines
and money can be made here only for the long term.
Okay, so the strategy in Zomato
is clear. Money can be made here for the long term.
Let's take the next question. Nanhe Lal
Verma told us. He has
100 shares of SpiceJet.  Avinash, please give your opinion on this, SpiceJet at a price of ₹ 7740 paise.
We had seen that when they inducted these new aircraft
in their fleet, there was a
rise in the stock, however,
this company has been battling with some controversies and some bad news as well.
SpiceJet and now this
stock price is around ₹. We are seeing
that there is some tension among the people, there are
chances of some restrictions on travel. Apart from this, Aakash
is also ready for launch now. You have
revealed the brand identity and your planes in Indian Skies,
so there will be some competition in the SpiceJet sector right now.
How do you
see the situation panning out for this
and would you also advise to remain neutral in this
or is it better that if you want to
buy something in the space, then go and bet on Indigo.
Abhishek, you are right that see,
in the airspace, firstly the price of crores is big,
secondly there is the issue of Corona or the Corona virus and the
biggest thing is that a new airline is going to come
in the private sector.  Obviously, if
this is presented from the perspective of a low-cost airline, then the
headwinds certainly
seem to be quite challenging for the company.
I feel that if we
talk about the airline space, Indi
is the best positioned. Even if competition comes,
they have a market share of 50%. So, in
my opinion, the cost
price and market price of the investor are more or
less similar. I feel that if
possible, they should shift to IndiGo.
If there is any company in the airline space
which is resilient and very strong from a balance sheet point of view and
capital allocation point of view, then it will be
IndiGo. So, in my opinion, they should
move to SpiceJet because the third quarter
numbers are also expected to be very poor
and there I feel that the
stock may fall further. So, I would
suggest that they shift to IndiGo and
keep a long-term horizon of at least
12 to 15 months as the
effects of Corona subside.  We feel
that here the rating will definitely
come first for the significant big player Indigo, so in my opinion, we should shift to Indigo.
Avinash ji, please
give your opinion regarding IDFC Bank, where is the problem,
why is this bank not doing well because we are
seeing that it is continuously stuck in the range of 40 to 0
and when the time of Covid
came, it went down even further,
where are the challenges for it and tell me that now these
discussions are going on that the year 2022 will be of
banking, it will be of financial, is
IDFC Bank a right place bank, is it a good place to
invest in this segment or should it
exit from here or should there be another strategy, if it
comes around 0 then it should be accelerated a little more,
Abhishek, I feel that look,
IDFC First Bank is such a bank which has
just converted from a bank to a retail bank
and here its Chief
Executive, Mr. Vaid Nathan, is from former
ICICI Bank, so the management
quality and bandwidth is very good and
secondly, looking at the CASA ratio,
almost  The company has reached 50. The company
declared good results in quarter two as well. The
management commentary is also very strong.
And the biggest thing is that
if in reality you know that
IDFC First Bank will
benefit a lot because they had already written off the exposure at 50 for it. In
my
opinion, this is a very cheap bank in the retail bank.
If someone wants to
take YNO exposure here for the long term, then
definitely there is no doubt that
value creation will come in the future. There were also
talks that there will be
a reverse merger between IDFC and IDFC First.
If this happens, then definitely the bank should
benefit a lot. So I feel that
in the coming year, the market will definitely watch the management on all these issues.
But the core banking business is doing very well.
In fact, they have
also entered into credit cards, which is very competitive
and is very cheap compared to other players.
So, in my opinion, the
bank is making a lot of efforts to
add new products and new customers in the retail sector. So, this is for the same
investors.  For those with a little patience,
this stock can definitely move.
If the fundamentals are so good, then we
definitely feel that in at least 12 to 15 months, a
near-term target of at least 65-70 can be achieved here.
Although this
is a slightly slow-moving stock, but on the
downside, I feel that whatever negatives are there are already
factored in in the price. So, for those
who want to buy for the long term, I
think this is still a very good price, but
obviously the time frame should be at least a year and a half.
Avinash ji, I will take your opinion on
this. Vipul ji has 20 shares and
their buying price is around the current price of
3021. This particular counter was
showing levels up to 5000 in the month of September
and now from there till now, we have seen a decline of 40.
We know that there are margin
pressures, but what would be your opinion, should we
exit this counter now and
could see a decline or are the
fundamentals strong?  And the future outlook
is positive. I think that if we
talk about Balaji Amines, yes the price correction
is quite significant, but we believe
that there are very few companies in plasticizers and amines
that operate on a large scale in India,
and
Balaji Amines is also present in that. I feel
that their product has application
in many sectors like
pharmaceuticals, agro chemicals,
specialty chemicals, so I feel
that somewhere there was a slight reduction in the price,
due to which a sell-off was seen in the stock.
I think in the coming session,
in the next six months and in the next one year, we
feel that if the market settles fully and there is
no price erosion, then
definitely a good profit can be made here. The
company has started expansion, it is
possible that
you may see some impact of this in 23, so in my opinion,
investors who have bought should have some
patience.  Keep in mind, I believe that this is one of those
companies which is definitely a large
player and cannot be ignored, so
I would suggest to Holden
not to be hasty in this, there is
no hurry in this, I am advising to stay in this stock,
Avinash ji, let's
take the question of the next viewer on
WhatsApp2 paisa price, Avinash ji, please
give your opinion on this, Mr. Renuka Sugar has
100 shares at a price of 33, we have seen that for
some time now the sugar stocks are
doing well because there used to be tension regarding surplus sugar due to
which the prices used to
fall a little and then they used to correct, now
support came from there and ethanol which is now a
factor, it also drove the company a little,
although a little below their buying
price, but if we look at it within a year,
this stock had shown a tremendous run up from 0 to 50,
what will be the advice now,
what should be the investment in Renuka Sugar,
see, this is the stock Abhishek,
definitely you have gone from No. 10 to almost 30,
so  There is no doubt that a
significant move has come, but
in this company, as you said, the next
trigger will be ethanol. The
management has already said that they
want to focus more on ethanol. And the
biggest thing to say about this company is that there are
unconfirmed reports that there are talks of
a big group or a big U-N-O
entity taking over this company in the future. So,
if such news flow comes, then there will
definitely be some more upside in the short term,
but I believe that at the
current levels, the risk-reward is definitely a little
low. If someone wants to stay invested, then
wait for some more price correction. There is no
doubt that in the coming year,
both ethanol and sugar
products
can see a lot of upside and a lot of traction,
but there is definitely a little correction, there is a
reaction, and only
if the stock comes to a slightly lower level, then there will be buying opportunities
and those who have it should hold it
because if this corporate development happens  If yes, then it has a
good re-
rating even from the current level.